(Leonard:)And mythological.
(Sheldon:)Irrelevant.
Yeah, I was studying
recombinant DNA technology...
...and I was confidant
I could create one...
(Sheldon:)...but my parents were unwilling to secure
the necessary eagle eggs and lion semen.
Of course, my sister got swimming lessons
when she wanted them.
(Howard:)Sheldon, not that we don't all enjoy
a good lion-semen story...
...but what's your point?
(Sheldon:)My point is, if Koothrappali is moving on
to a new life of shallow, undeserved fame...
...then perhaps this is an opportunity
to create a better cohort.
You wanna breed a new friend?
(Sheldon:)That's one option, but who has the time?
(Sheldon:)But consider this.
(Sheldon:)The Japanese, they're doing some
wonderful work with artificial intelligence.
Now, combine that with some animatronics
from the imagineers over at Disney.
Next thing you know, we're playing "Halo"
with a multilingual Abraham Lincoln.